<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="bicycle_crunches">Bicycle crunches</string>
    <string name="heel_touch">Heel touch</string>
    <string name="jumping_jacks">Jumping jacks</string>
    <string name="leg_raises">Leg raises</string>
    <string name="military_push_ups">Military push ups</string>
    <string name="mountain_climber">Mountain climber</string>
    <string name="plank">Plank</string>
    <string name="push_ups">Push ups</string>
    <string name="reverse_crunches">Reverse crunches</string>
    <string name="russian_twist">Russian twist</string>
    <string name="side_crunches">Side crunches</string>
    <string name="sit_ups">Sit-ups</string>


    <string name="bicycle_crunches_description">Lift one leg just off the ground and extend it out.
        Lift the other leg and bend your knee towards your chest. As you do so twist through your core so the
        opposite arm comes towards the raised knee. You don\'t need to touch elbow to knee,
        instead focus on moving through your core as you turn your torso.
    </string>
    <string name="heel_touch_description">
        Lay down with your back on the ground and your knees bent and pointed towards the ceiling.
        With your arms on your side raise your shoulders slightly off the ground.
        Using your abs rotate your right hand down to your right foot and then back up.
        Then do the same thing with your left hand. Alternate back and forth for the desired amount of repetitions.
    </string>
    <string name="jumping_jacks_description">
        Stand upright with your legs together, arms at your sides. Bend your knees slightly, and jump into the air.
        As you jump, spread your legs to be about shoulder-width apart. Stretch your arms out and over your head.
        Jump back to starting position. Repeat.
    </string>
    <string name="leg_raises_description">
        Lie on your back, legs straight and together. Keep your legs straight and lift them all the way up to the ceiling until
        your butt comes off the floor. Slowly lower your legs back down till they\'re just above the floor. Hold for a moment.
        Raise your legs back up. Repeat.
    </string>
    <string name="military_push_ups_description">
        Get down on all fours, placing your hands slightly wider than your shoulders. Straighten your arms and legs.
        Lower your body until your chest nearly touches the floor. Pause, then push yourself back up. Repeat.
    </string>
    <string name="mountain_climber_description">
        Put both hands and knees on the floor.
        Place your right foot near your right hand and extend your left leg behind you.
        In one smooth motion, switch your legs, keeping your arms in the same position.
        Switch your legs back and forth twice, such that your right leg is again close to your right hand.
    </string>
    <string name="plank_description">
        Plant hands directly under shoulders like you’re about to do a push-up.
        Ground toes into the floor and squeeze glutes to stabilize your body. Your legs should be working, too
        — be careful not to lock or hyperextend your knees.
        Neutralize your neck and spine by looking at a spot on the floor about a foot beyond your hands.
        Your head should be in line with your back.
    </string>
    <string name="push_ups_description">
        Get down on all fours, placing your hands slightly wider than your shoulders. Straighten your arms and legs.
        Lower your body until your chest nearly touches the floor. Pause, then push yourself back up. Repeat.
    </string>
    <string name="reverse_crunches_description">
        Start lying down with your arms by your sides. Raise your legs so your thighs are perpendicular
        to the floor and your knees are bent at a 90° angle. Breathe out and contract your abs to bring
        your knees up towards your chest and raise your hips off the floor.
        Hold for a beat in this position, then slowly lower your legs back to the starting position.
    </string>
    <string name="russian_twist_description">
        Root into your sit bones as you lift your feet from the floor, keeping your knees bent.
        Elongate and straighten your spine at a 45-degree angle from the floor, creating a V shape with your torso and thighs.
        Reach your arms straight out in front, interlacing your fingers or clasping your hands together.
        Use your abdominals to twist to the right, then back to center, and then to the left.
    </string>
    <string name="side_crunches_description">
        Lie down on the floor or mat in a conventional sit-up position with legs at roughly a 90-degree angle and foot planted on the ground.
        Do not let your feet come up during this exercise. Place your hands behind your head on either side, keep your elbows pointing out.
        Lift your right shoulder blade off the floor and then drive your elbow in the direction of your left knee.
        Keep your chin off your chest and not pulling your head and neck.
        Squeeze at the top of the movement and then slowly release back to the starting position. Repeat the movement.
    </string>
    <string name="sit_ups_description">
        Lie down on your back. Bend your legs and place feet firmly on the ground to stabilize your lower body.
        Cross your hands to opposite shoulders or place them behind your ears, without pulling on your neck.
        Curl your upper body all the way up toward your knees. Exhale as you lift.
        Slowly, lower yourself down, returning to your starting point. Inhale as you lower.
    </string>






</resources>